<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0">
	<channel>
		<title>SpagoBI news</title>
		<link>http://spagobi.eng.it</link>
		<description>SpagoBi News</description>
		<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>10 Feb 2006 09:13:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
		<generator>RSS generator</generator>
		<item>
           	<title>SpagoBI roadmap</title>
			<description>
				The new SpagoBI roadmap for 2006 is out, we hope answering your needs. You can see the new plan to the http://spagobi.eng.it/SpagoBISiteENG/target/docs/roadmap.html link. If you want to contribute to reach it, don’t hesitate to write us ! 
		     </description>
			<link>http://localhost:8080/portal</link>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">summary-1054822375</guid>
			<pubDate>10 Feb 2006 09:13:00 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
           	<title>Business Intelligence with SpagoBI</title>
			<description>
				The SpagoBI team activated training courses on the platform broaching the Business Intelligence themes. First editions will take place in France and in Italy, others will be planned during the year. 
		     </description>
			<link>http://localhost:8080/portal</link>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">summary-1054822376</guid>
			<pubDate>10 Feb 2006 09:13:00 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
     		<item>
                	<title>SpagoBI version 1.8 released: eXo platform v2</title>
			<description>
				The SpagoBI platform 1.8 has been released on 10 february 2006. The new version is based on eXo platform v2 and it can use the eXo jsr 170 implementation. 
		        </description>
			<link>http://localhost:8080/portal</link>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">summary-1054822377</guid>
			<pubDate>10 Feb 2006 09:13:00 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
                	<title>SpagoBI version 1.8 released: maven 2 compilation</title>
			<description>
				The compilation and packaging of the SpagoBI 1.8 version source code is based on maven2. The compilation can be done for different application servers and makes easier the installation process.
		        </description>
			<link>http://localhost:8080/portal</link>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">summary-1054822378</guid>
			<pubDate>10 Feb 2006 09:13:00 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
     		<item>
                	<title>SpagoBI platform: Tomcat, JBoss and JOnAS certificated</title>
			<description>
				SpagoBI has been tested with JOnAS, Tomcat and JBoss. For each application server has been released a step by step installation guide and a package containing all the useful installation files, in order to facilitate the task. 
		        </description>
			<link>http://localhost:8080/portal</link>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">summary-1054822379</guid>
			<pubDate>30 Jan 2006 09:13:00 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
                <item>
                <title>SpagoBI source code moved to the ObjectWeb SVN repository</title>
			<description>
			The source code of the SpagoBI project has been moved to the SVN repository of the ObjectWeb Consortium. To connect access to the SpagoBI's ObjectWeb page and select the SVN tab.  
		        </description>
			<link>http://localhost:8080/portal</link>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">summary-1054822380</guid>
			<pubDate>30 Jan 2006 14:13:00 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
